magicbid.com 2010-11-26

# MagicBid - PRIVACY

**PRIVACY POLICY**

* * *

MagicBid.COM ("Magic Bid ") respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. The following Privacy Policy outlines the information Magic Bid may collect and how we may use that information.

**In General**

* * *

Magic Bid  is a service provided by  Magic Shopping Solutions Pvt Ltd(hereinafter referred to as “Magic Shopping Solutions” or “We”). We understand and value your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all aspects relating to collecting data while you are visiting the Magic Bid website.   
By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective on acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective 10 days after being posted on the website. 

**Collecting Data**

* * *

Personally Identifiable Information (or Personal Information) is information that can be used to identify or contact you. When you visit our Website, we collect only the Personal Information you provide to us. We collect the Personal Information that you provide to us in two general and distinct ways: (1) when you register, and (2) when you choose to use various Website Services or participate in surveys or send emails to us.

We also collect non-personal information from you and about your use of our Website, emails, special promotions and newsletters that we send to you, and Websites of selected sponsors and advertisers, your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Magic Bid, ad data, IP address and standard web log information and information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data. For example, we may use "cookies" or "web beacons" to collect non-personal information about your use of our site, selected sponsors' sites, or emails we send to you. Magic Bid does not store any Personal Information in any cookies on your computer. We do not use web beacons to collect any Personal Information from or about you or to track your activities across Websites generally. All of these are described in more detail below. 

**Registration and Member Profile**

* * *

You may use our Website without registering or submitting any Personal Information. In that case, the only information we collect will be non-personal information collected through the use of cookies or web beacons (see details below). However, in order to have access to certain services and content available on our site you are required to complete a registration form. We use the Personal Information that you provide through registration to respond to questions from you and/or inform you of significant changes to this Privacy Policy. We may also use this information to send you emails with special promotions or newsletters with content that we think may be of interest to you. You can always opt-out of receiving such emails or unsubscribe to newsletters at the time you register or at any time. 

**Data Usage**

* * *

Personal Information is primarily used to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: 

  * provide the services and customer support you request; 
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions; 
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; 
  * inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers; and 
  * compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties. 

**E-mail and SMS Newsletters**

* * *

Magic Bid may collect anonymous, non-personal information about your use of e-mails and newsletters that we send to you.   
When you register with Magic Bid, you agree to receive e-mail and SMS newsletters. We will use this method to inform you of new functions or special promotions on our website. You can at any time opt-out of these by changing your settings under My Account -> Edit Profile 

**Public Forums**

* * *

This Privacy Policy does not  _protect_  you when you use our public forums. You should be aware that any information shared in a chat room, bulletin board, posting or online discussion is public information and may be seen, disclosed to or collected by third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy. You should think carefully before disclosing any personal information in any public forum.

**Children**

* * *

Magic Bid adheres to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. in each of our Web sites. Parents can help by spending time online with children and monitoring children's online use. Please help us protect children's privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on this site or any other without your permission.

Magic Bid does not 

 _collect_  and keep any personal information from persons who Magic Bid actually knows are under 18 years of age.

**Disclosure of your Information**

* * *

We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity.  
Except as set forth in this Privacy  _Policy_  or as specifically agreed to by you, we will not disclose any Personal Information gathered from you on our Website. We may release Personal Information to third parties: (1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (2) in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others.

**Magic Bid User Name**

* * *

Once you have been approved as registered user with Magic Bid, you will be required to choose a user name. This user name will be displayed throughout Magic Bid and therefore provided to the public. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, users will not be able to personally identify your activities on Magic Bid.  
When visiting Magic Bid from a public or shared computer, certain information about you, such as your user name, may also be visible to others who may use such the computer after your use.

**Viewing/Changing Personal Data**

* * *

You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to Magic Bid at any time. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or information is inaccurate. 

**Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account**

* * *

Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our General Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.  
You can delete or deactivate your Magic Bid account at any time. When you delete your membership, your personal data is removed from our database unless we are required to save the data. As a rule it takes two to three business days until your information is completely removed from all records. 

**The Use of Cookies at our Website**

* * *

Magic Bid uses “cookies”, which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject our cookie, certain of the functions and conveniences of our site may not work properly but you do not have to accept our cookie in order to productively use our site. While it may be possible to link non-personal cookie information to Personal Information collected in other ways, we want you to know that if you accept our cookie we will not, without your consent, link the cookie information we collect to Personal Information you provide to us on our site.

**Security Measures**

* * *

Your Magic Bid account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Magic Bid will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Magic Bid site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.  
Further, We treat data as an asset that must be protected. We use lots of security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam**

* * *

Magic Bid assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms of Use. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by “web crawlers” or “web spiders” to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

**Data Protection Guidelines**

* * *

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 10 days after they are initially posted on the site.

**Questions?**

* * *

If you have a privacy question about Magic  Bid, please email us at support@MagicBid.com
